every day on the hermit craft server
something new weird and wonderful pops
up and today is no exception because
this wonderful machine made by
mumbo-jumbo has just popped up and I
have no idea what it is to anyone that
has run into issues with their skin this
machine is for you
it will undone Belen II player who walks
into it important do not use this skin
unjam blur if your skin is not jumbled I
mean I don't know about you but that
sounds a bit like an invitation hold on
we will give it a go so what happens if
you use it when you're not jug board Oh
blimey oh wow what's it done heck it's
given me a beard pretty sure it took
these off what on earth I'm not sure I
understand what's going on here hold on
let me let me let me let me let me get
my camera count on let's have a look at
what this is doing okay hold on hold on
let me just move my head a little bit is
the back of knotch agreein oh I love
this oh I love this so much hold on is
it there's a stress monster up there
let's go let's go let's go show her okay
we are we a Hunchback of Notre agreein
let's put on our Electra oh my goodness
what does that look like okay this is
gonna be good she's gonna be so confused
that she figured out what's going on
what's with your head I see no problem I
see no problems here sorry to be the
bearer of bad news
you don't like my head
[Music]
okay we need to let's go back into the
skin and jungler ow and let's do this
one more time
back to green again what's it done
what's it done this time let's have a
look oh well this is normal
that's hold on let me get this the
realest of our hands there we go perfect
perfect wait that's my head not my feet
oh this is weird
look at my hand it's all red okay yeah
let's go back let's try this one more
time shall we to get rid of our
upside-down this going back to color
anything Oh whoo you know I think we
should stay like this for a while see if
you if you tilt your head just the right
angle you can see it oh this is an
abomination
but abomination is there anything on how
to get back when you press the button
stand within the lamps yeah yeah
multicolored mist or green marking the
process is complete before you leave
reset the machine by pressing the button
again make sure you stay outside of labs
otherwise I honestly I don't know what
will happen oh and by the way this cost
20 it's cuz 20 diamonds oh no oh no I
just wasted 60 diamonds on this I think
we're gonna we gotta go do we gonna go
to choice dress this one thing went
wrong something went wrong stress help
help help
if you talk just at the right time when
the when the when the arm goes up it's
like help me I've wasted you know I I
don't want to waste more diamonds on
this I think I might have to stay like
this for a while what a waste of 60
diamonds
I should have this is this is me well
over I don't read the book I don't read
the book that's the issue I have I don't
read books all the way through and then
I end up having to pay a fortune I'm not
paying another 20 diamonds to get back
to normal
her forever ever ever forever friend it
looks like I'm shaking my head you know
what later on today mumbo and I and if
you others are going to be playing a
little bit of this game which I spoke
about briefly before and it's time it's
actually ready to play and I'm hoping we
can play later so I'm gonna show mumbo
what his machine is done what he's done
to me but also while we're here no one
is buying this stupid building so we
need to make it even cheaper for sale 20
diamonds please buy come on 20 diamonds
20 diamonds for all this work
someone please please one earth have you
done mate what have I done what have you
done it said don't do this if your skin
is normal and I was like yeah I'm
totally gonna do this yeah and then this
happened it looks like I got it looks
like I got run over the problem that I
have is your arm moving as it looks like
it's like you're kind of kind of talking
it's not it's not it's not a good
situation mate I mean I am actually kind
of envious though I feel like I now have
the most unexcited skin
I went from really hating having a
disgusting horrible skin to now being
jealous of how much of a mess your skin
is because I was pressing the button
that having a great time and then I
realized I didn't actually read the
whole book and it shot you charged 20
diamonds this is a money-making scheme
I'm great I'm gonna check back in at the
last minute because it's Cowell was the
only person that had a jumbled up skin
so I was like well I'll take 20 I take
20 of this gal okay yeah not thinking
that anyone else is actually going to
leave yeah I'm actually I'm quids in
[Laughter]
well I mean yeah you've made you've made
a meal of it but we're gonna have to
pause now because we're gonna be playing
some boom box with tango so yeah yeah
right I mean yeah I just it's gonna be
so distracting
imagine order blown up just imagine
let's come around the corner go back a
tiny bit more when it's just the eyes
people oh dear okay well I never thought
making this machine but I thought this
would end the silliness but it seems
fantastic absolutely fantastic that's
the Hermit quaff right I guess anyway
yes should we do some exploding of
people yeah let's get this place
gentlemen ladies ready to blow each
other up I believe so I think so some
boom box to keep it real quick it's a
game about blowing up your friends is
red team versus blue team you're gonna
in the floor there's gonna these little
crates you picking up TNT and drop it on
the floor and blow up the opponent in
the in the outside areas there's special
power-ups in the walls that are like
armor and potions and stuff like that
and the idea is that you have to
infiltrate the enemy base going through
the a little obsidian area blow up a
wall get a flag and bring it back to
your base and drop it in the crate down
there and get a point and that'll light
up one of these lights here first one to
three wins capture flags blow stuff up
example two flags blow things up are you
ready squad do we have any tactical like
plans for things that they should do I
mean I spent most of the time just
looking at myself everything I took
you try this yet tilt your head to the
side it genuinely looks like I'm
squashed I mean it is you know a city I
didn't quite understand what you meant i
tilted my minecraft head to the side I
realize now rotate whenever I'm looking
at you I'm gonna I'm gonna I'm gonna
rotate my video so that you actually
look like you are standing on the whole
world shifts for greeing ready 3 Oh give
me what I need the toilet no okay wait
do we go the same way or do we split up
do we split up no that's a bad move
isn't it spinning ups always back I know
Karen mm okay I've got nothing in that
barrel all right
I'm in the middle okay good I think I
got I've got I've got 14 PT I would just
thought I'd see what that was did you
not see my technical abilities now I
just did some serious maneuvers man oh
man oh no this is bad news
this is bad news for me because I fight
my own to protection is in the middle i
got t/od I'm going for it are you well
I'm sneaking into their base lead you
and I'm sneaking into their base I'm
probably so huge yeah that's a big one
I'm gonna take this I break I break the
the couple's young right
yeah what green they might be in our
base - we totally didn't think about
defense chief or this really yeah
possibly
Kimberly I'm coming in coming in halt
please - they're totally in our baby
Oh No hope you got FCAT there you go one
way in one way out I got it well I bring
my I almost blew myself up did I get
Irina's you get the plague yes I got the
flag I got it back I got a flag guys
making the return place that right next
to ah I'll go for it I'm gonna play it
back oh no I have to pay in the back
have you gone have you captured one we
go one we go in with one one no way one
point up hey deal he's that he's that
he's that my own stupidity I didn't
understand them I couldn't was in our
base and she's just trying to blow me up
I've got no TNT
you are trapped I think I think they
know man they know I'm invisible so you
guys scored a point right yeah we got to
play think so yes yes yes yes I'm gonna
take green green teams base I'm going to
capture their flag someone else's flag
oh all right replenish well good well
yeah you haven't we have to fill up our
smoker actually Oh what are we put in
there again tango hey take that take
that take that potion you go invisible
as well I wicked come on okay you can
have a backup
go in go in quickly quickly quickly
quickly Mambo go back there take the
slow one on both my legs like take that
invisibility potion around the corner
and then we can both sneak with the the
final two together how you can take a
flag I could take a [\h__\h] right have you
not been invisible at all yet no it's
just camp in us have you got have you
taken the potion number yeah I can see
you have grab and creep grab that flag
grab that flag and then head head out
with me oh yeah oh okay okay so my
somewhere but I've got one heart left
you go you got a place it in the pacing
of the barrel no nope shake up shake up
shake up sit hey I've got so little
health even the smallest little tap is
gonna put me over the edge cubbies
cubbies taking up a flag it's two to two
next number if you get in with this flag
I'm gonna block it I can block come in
quickly okay okay okay and what do I
just throw it in where are you I'm
coming
oh no no I think I just let come out I
just let come out he's here oh my
goodness yes stressful game I have the
sweatiest armpits what's the prize my
skin has only just returned back to
normal dude there is no way I'm right
element we are here for the championship
game team green and team Mambo cha cha
would Exuma so I'm hello to the new big
Zoomer didn't even improve yep wait wait
a bit harsh I should have clarified but
new role you can only have one flag out
per team at a time okay so no no to be
flattered okay okay all right ready I'm
you guys ready I'm ready
one defense one offense one defeated
offense in the offense
with a cheesy cheese I will be defense
okay whoever gets TNT first defense I
think the fence is priority yeah that's
that's a good way to do it yeah all
right guys let them right god I feel so
professional in this one three I don't
have any
all right you go offense n collect them
on the way okay yes good move do you
reckon go through the middle yeah I
don't think they'll be expecting it so
hard when they're moving yes so I'm
doing a terrible am i defending oh we've
just remembered yeah I'm offense on I
yeah maybe offense
I'm a fan right stop it I'll know that
Zoomer in Zephyr timing in there is
actually afk like just off to one side
and I keep seeing an actual name tagging
on my own zoom is the baby careful all
right get out of there
well I'm in my car I'm in an ad I'm in
their HQ though okay good good good good
good cuz this isn't going well for me
really they through the wall yep
I can't do anything about this I'm
pretty sure I've discovered work I think
I'm gonna get zeph but I've run out TT
really I've run out of TNT yeah I was I
was trying to defend that they know
Kiefer V at bay where's curve I need to
go for curb because he's got the flat
he's not cubbies Exuma I'm sorry Zoomer
what do you mean where is he who's this
comfort that you keep talking I've lost
the game kills you back they got
anything on the points number you need
to return with the flag I know
but now cup knows who I am one down I'm
I'm sneaking it behind cup fan really
he's still alive somehow I just I'm a
little hell where are they
I have an enderpearl I can't use know if
we're both stuck in here what are you
doing
okay okay okay okay because we can only
have one flag at a time we've really
flawed ourselves here well if you get
through I can be waiting too with
another one right yeah I can also I can
also hide and stop them I just I'm
guessing so what I can see is user names
I see you I do I just got it I'm to the
point
yeah I gotta collect another one good to
collect what my I'm ready I'm ready I'm
ready to collect the other one we need
to try and replenish our wool if we can
oh you guys got a point
nice yeah hey right there keep bug hey
I'm scouring the outside and get one of
those items that would be huge right oh
that would be big I thought would be big
said half knows I'm here oh great
how's that ass wait is that up in there
is that - I think on a second point how
do they do that I made it out joy Miriam
is on fire okay I need to just I'm
making it red for it I'm gonna go same
with you I would defend you if you go to
collect another one we fixed we need to
exchange things quicker you get you go
straight for their flag cuz by the time
you get there I'll have put this one in
cool we got two boys of death I'm so
pleased to death Oh
that could've that could be it they only
need one more oh you guys have a few
points - yeah we have two points oh my
gosh oh my goodness we wanna we're on a
showdown - Murray's behind me hold on I
have an idea - do I wonder if anyone all
my goodness I have got some serious I
got potion of swiftness I've got I've
got potion of invisibility and I've got
one for you as well dude I've got two
for you swiftness and invisibility it's
great I like green because I've got the
stun for you I've got the staff that's
just made it out
I didn't even block it okay so I've got
he's right there said eff has almighty
team they've got the flag and I can't
stop them mum by pleased
I've got potion of swiftness they're
gonna capture the flag I can't even a
single oh I've got a booty straight past
everyone I'm trying to catch you so I
can give you this version of swiftness
I think who has the fly you must be ZF I
think it's a son I don't have any tea
did they score it it was it was Exuma
Seema had eczema how did they trade it
apparently oh that is since me no Exuma
that sneaky sneaky exumai seem that did
you do a little switcheroo we switch
double switcheroo he's switched it to
Exuma who isn't even Exuma
what do you mean it's a mega switch GG
guys yeah well my guys well gentlemen
laughs and azuma great games great game
congratulations congratulations you win
members copper or something but I got
nothing for you here you guys get this
torch
[Applause]
my first birthday all over that was a
lot of fun boombox has definitely been
one of the more complicated minigames I
hope you enjoyed it as please let me
know in the comments if you did we
should probably play a little bit more
of this in fact I think one of the
episodes that I'd like to do is kind of
go through and play all of the minigames
the mini game extravaganza because the
the district has actually buy ice why
would I buy ice I I think that there's
wow it's just exciting it's basically a
theme park now and I don't think I've
made the most of it so maybe we could
get together a small group of people and
do like a tournament a kind of thing
anyway that is it for today's episode
but before we say goodbye but I need to
sort something out and that's that's my
skin and there's like I mean look that's
my ridiculous I need to go back to my
base really quick because I'm not paying
mumbo anymore diamonds to mess up my
skin but I think I know a way to fix
this okay so in order to get back to
normal we're gonna have to essentially
completely squish ourselves and to do
that we make a little squishing device
there we go simple as that and that in
theory because I'm this way hold on let
me let me take some cuz I'm this way
that [\h__\h] squash me back to the way that
I was before so it's as simple as that I
hit the lever and it should squash me
back to where I was
essentially saving 20 diamonds because
I'm a bit of a mess you see I am a bit
of a mess
so let's do this so we hop in here and
all we do is three - what
and didn't work hey we're back to normal
brilliant okay what happens if you
squish yourself even more well either
way that is enough for today's video I
shall see you in the next one thank you
very much for watching and good